<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:40:56 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/overview/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:11:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/overview/</guid><description>What is Telego? # This library was designed to be the one-to-one implementation of Telegram Bot API, with all methods and types represented in Go code. It&amp;rsquo;s also, easy-to-use and understand, because of the same naming and types as described in Telegram API with as small as possible differences. Telego provides almost all comments and descriptions in godoc.
Since using bare methods and types is not so convenient, Telego gives you a lot of helpers, utilities, and even update handlers with predicates.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:11:08 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/quick-start/</guid><description>Where to start? # If you are a complete beginner and/or have no experience with Telegram Bots or don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start, highly suggest first reading Bots: An introduction for developers in order to understand what bots can do. If you have questions about how to create/modify a bot or what is a bot token, that is also described in the introduction for developers.
If you are familiar with bots capabilities, but still don&amp;rsquo;t know how they work, you can read at least some parts of the API reference:</description></item><item><title>Tutorial</title><link>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/tutorial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:11:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://telego.pixelbox.dev/docs/introduction/tutorial/</guid><description>Introduction # In this tutorial, you will see different parts of a library used to create a simple &amp;ldquo;echo&amp;rdquo; bot with more in depth explanation and different ways to do the same thing.
You will create bot, set different settings, call Telegram to get bot user, start getting updates with specified parameters, use helper method to get updates, handle updates in simple loop, create new bot handler, use general purpose handlers, use message handler, call Telegram method to send message, use Telego utils to simplify methods usage and use With.</description></item></channel></rss>